Subscribe to the YouTube channel
AllBankWater.com and press the bell icon
to watch the video first.
Friends, in this video we will tell you
important information related to your IDFC Bank account. Friends, with this you
can open an account online from home. In this
you get two types of accounts. The
first is your IDFC account in
which you have to maintain Rs. 10,000
and in this you can avail all the facilities like ATM card, cheque book,
internet banking, mobile banking
and the second
is your FD account in
which you have to make a minimum ID of Rs. 10,000
and this account goes to your zero balance
and as long as your FD continues in it, your
account will say your zero balance and in
return you will also get a credit card of ₹10. So
friends, let's start the video
and tell you how you
can open an account. For this, you have to type ICICI Bank
in Google or whatever browser you use.
So, see, we have typed it here
and after that the ICICI Bank
website is opening here.  Friends, to
open this account, you must have your Aadhar card and
mobile repairing and you must
also have a PAN card, only then will you be
able to open this account, so see, here the
option to open your savings account
is showing, you can open your savings account from here by clicking here,
now you will see that here you are showing an option from
where you
can open your account from here also, so we have to
click on this supply button and
after that
you have to internet here the mobile number and email ID which you
want to register in your account, so we
internet here and click on the continue button
and after that it is asking for our PAN card
number, so we have
also entered our PAN card number here and
after that we will click on the continue button, as soon as
we continue, an
OTP will come on our mobile which is for your PAN card
verification, so we will make the
payment here by looking at our OTP from our mobile and
after that we will click on the continue button,
so in this way you can verify your PAN card here
and  As soon as your PAN
card is verified,
you will receive an OTP for your Aadhaar card verification.
Print your Aadhaar card here and
then click on the Continue button.
As soon as you click on Continue,
your Aadhaar card verification will be
received on your mobile.
From there, you can complete your Aadhaar verification by looking at your OTP.
As soon as you complete your Aadhaar verification,
you will see that your next page will
open. Now friends, here
you have to fill your personal details on Next. After filling
your personal details, you will
click on the Continue button here.
Look, our next page has opened here, in
which your personal details like whether
you are married or unmarried, whether you do business
or service, what is your
source of income, what is your education
qualification and what is your income
range, you will enter all these details
and after that click on the Continue button.
OK, then
enter your details according to your profile and after that
click on the posting button like
You will continue, you will see that on next it is
asking for your normal details, for which you
want to make Navami in your account,
you will enter his name here,
after that you have to enter his date of birth
and after that you have to show what is your relation with the nominee,
like whether she is your mother
or sister or brother or wife, whatever it is,
you will enter your relationship there
and after that you will click on the continue button, so
friends, as you continue,
you will see that your details will start showing on the next page
and along with that you will see that
your address details are showing here,
2010 is on your Aadhar card, it is
automatically solving it here,
if you want to make any change in it, then
you can change it, like if
you want to reduce any of your communication, then
you
also get the option to change your Kundli here and you can
just click on your communication and 10 years
and after that you can click on the continue button, so
see our communication
address  And Parmanand is the same, so we do
n't have to make any changes, we
click on the continue button here, so see, we have
clicked on the continue button here and
all the details that you have filled here are showing, once
you do your proof here, now you
can check all the details from here whether whatever
you have done retail internet is correct
or wrong, so after checking here, you will
click on the submit button,
an OTP will come on your number, you will
print the DPI and confirm its details
and it will be submitted,
so as soon as you submit here, you will
see that on the next page, your
option for funding is coming, if you
want to transfer some of your funds to your account, you
can do that, otherwise you will
continue it by clicking on its family button
and you will see that your account will be
successfully activated here and your
account number will also be shown at the top, from
here you can also generate your account number and your
internet banking user ID and password,
so friends,
if you liked this video then  Like this video
and subscribe to our channel
because we keep bringing more new information for you on this channel,
so do subscribe to this channel
friends, if
you are still facing any problem
in opening the account then you can contact me,
our email id is
visible on the display in front of you, you can send this
voice mail or you
can comment to us, we will definitely reply to you, so
friends, that's all for today, see you
Madhuri, in this video
we will tell you
how you can paste the video KYC of your account,
for this you must subscribe to this channel
and also press the bell button so
that
you keep getting the notification of our next video and you
can be the first to watch the video, so friends,
thank you, see you in the next video, Jai
Hind
[Music]